hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jeremiah Kowski in this podcast I talk
about how coaches trainers and mentors
can scale their businesses to multiple
six and seven figures and I want to talk
to you about having a business that fits
your lifestyle designing your life in a
way that truly is something that you
feel confident about so you're not
spending all this these hours building
your business here's the thing in the
coaching business online course business
one of the best ways to make money on
the planet that I know of uh I see
people that they just spend way too much
time putting all the pieces together way
too much time getting the foundation set
up way too much time doing stuff that is
not actually going to bring in cash flow
for them and listen this isn't something
for you to feel guilty about or ashamed
of I've done the same thing myself I
think that it's a natural thing that
happens to people that we end up having
a vision for what we want to do we have
an idea for what we want to build in our
business and then we just uh come up
with all of these tasks that we have to
do all we see all the stuff that has to
get done and if you have taken any
courses if you taken any training or
coaching that's out there you know that
it can get really complicated here's the
problem we overco complicate the process
and we think we need to do 90% more than
we actually need to to build our
business and so what I encourage people
to do is to this is this is in my life
I've done this myself as well what's the
life I want to live how many hours do I
want to work and then I fit my business
into
that and so if you want to be working
100 hours a week which God who wants to
do that but if you want to I mean
there's a ton of stuff that you can do
in your business but I'll tell you this
there's diminishing returns and you're
not really going to actually make more
money by doing those things it's better
to figure out how to build your business
on less than 10 to 15 hours a week and
have something that is truly impacting
people that's that's making the kind of
cash flow that you want to make cash
flow is King it's the most important
thing in your business and making sure
that it's bringing in the finances that
you need and so what we do is we work
backwards and we say okay what is the
most important thing in my business and
for most people there's there's two
things they need to get more sales and
have consistency of sales so how do you
get more people to buy your stuff and
then how do you get those same people to
buy more of your stuff stuff and that
compounds and then they stay
consistently buying from you over time
long term that's why I love the
membership model building a membership
with courses and training and mentoring
and you put together something that
people can be a part of that they want
to be a part of longterm so you have
reoccurring Revenue which is awesome and
so here's the problem investing all of
this time in mapping out your course
planning out what you're going to do
coming up with all the best practices
and ways that you're going to make it
perfect that does not translate to
financial gain in your business no
matter how much you think it does and
most people think it
does what translate the most is the is
one
thing getting in front of people who
have a problem that you can solve and
then persuading them
that you can solve that problem for them
and directly persuading those same
people at the same moment in time to
make a financial investment with you
into your course or your coaching
program and so those things have to
happen for you to have a sustainable
business all of the other stuff is bonus
and extra if you're not doing those two
those two or three things you get new
people on your email list and then they
get to watch presentations with you
video
presentations and then in those video
presentations they become sold or
pre-old and then they are ready to make
an investment because they have heard
what they need to hear to trust you in
order to buy the thing that you are
selling selling and so that's a whole
process of
sales and and and not anything slimy or
sleazy it's a process of taking people
that truly have a problem that you can
truly help and and finding the real
people that you really can help getting
them connected to you showing them
demonstrating that you can solve that
problem for
them and then moving them from
well I'm
interested to increase their level
of yes let's do it yes let's go after it
yes let's take action increasing that
level in their mind in their emotional
state in their belief
systems that they are ready to take
action that they know that this is going
to help
them and and none of this has to do with
information
none of this has to do with dialing in
the perfect course or the perfect
branding or the perfect
website okay it has everything to do
with just three three
things you create
offers that connect with people that
solve a problem for
them a very specific problem for them
you get them and persuade them to to
take time out of their busy
schedule to listen to
you and that's the key right there is if
you can get people to take time out of
their busy schedule to listen to you
because most
people are going to come up with a
thousand to one reasons why they are way
too busy to listen to whatever you have
to offer so how do we do
this we come up with an irresistible
offer and the words that we write the
sales copy
communicates the value in a very
specific strategic pointed way to that
specific person and so we we really get
into their psychology what do they want
more than anything else what does that
person desire more than anything else
and if you don't know what that is
that's what our job is that's our number
one job is to figure out what is that
thing that people want more than
anything else and then we can give it to
them and we give it to them truly and
impactfully and in fact we're not just
charging we're not charging money to
give it to them we actually give it to
them for
free and this is the part where people
get a little bit confused because
they're like wait if I'm giving them
what they truly need for free why why
are they ever going to buy anything from
me it's because when you give them what
they need for
free you've built Trust
and there's something next that they
need and so it's identifying not the one
thing that somebody needs but what is
the one thing and then the next thing
and then the next thing and the next
thing and then you build a
sequence of connecting with that person
solving that problem for them and then
offering them to solve the rest of their
problems as well for a
fee and so then by doing that because
you already solved one problem you built
trust with those
people now we can charge money by
solving the problem for them after that
and the real key behind all of this is
the ability to communicate the ability
to to
talk in a way that persuades people that
gets them to take action that gets them
to say
okay I like what's getting thrown down
here I can buy into this I'm seeing it I
understand it I think I can make this
work for me yes this is going to work
for me and that's the moment that you
want to get people to where they're not
just saying wow that's interesting
information
like you want you want to know the
number one praise that nauseates me more
than anything else wow Jeremiah that was
great information nauseates me because I
know that that's not a sale that's the
worst thing somebody could ever say to
me wow that was great information I mean
I appreciate it when people say that but
like they they mean well but like it's
in my business it means I
failed okay it really does because what
I want people to go from is Way Beyond
just wow that's great
information
to Holy
bleep this is going to work for me and
I'm ready to jump in and I'm ready to
take action and I'm ready to do the work
to get it to work for me and when when
you can get somebody that place they
will buy whatever you have to
sell they will buy and stay with you
long term because they're hooked they're
connected they're bought
in and I want to tell you this if you're
somebody who is apprehensive about
getting people to buy into something
with you and stay longterm you need to
possibly address that internally and
realize that that's what business is
that's what this business the course
business the online coaching business is
is understanding that when you can learn
how to make that connection with
somebody you connect with somebody
around their dream desire and you become
the person who gives them the very thing
that they desire better than anybody
else they've ever met before and that's
what our clients say that we do for them
is that we give them the thing that they
desired more than anything else like my
client Dr shandu if he was able to take
a test campaign and make six figures
with it or or like Ian Carroll who just
after try and some of what we do was
able to make over $40,000 a month
consistently in his coaching and
mentoring business and that's what I
love to do with people I love to take
them from where you're at right now to
being able to have
consistent cash flow and income in their
business so when you understand what is
it that really truly drives and
motivates people and gets them to buy in
with you and you can persuade them that
working with you making that invest
vment is worth their
time you have a business and now you
just find more people to run through the
same process you just find more people
to put through that same process so if I
can get a hundred people to watch my
presentation and 20 of them become a
client which are pretty good numbers 20
of them become a client
because what they heard that wasn't just
good information to them but it was like
whoa this is going to work and then they
make an
investment let's say I'm selling
something that's
$2,000 to cost
me 20 bucks to get those 100 people all
right let's do the math here 20 bucks to
get those 100
people that's $2,000
okay pretty decent for an ad
spend and we were able to get 20 people
to
purchase at
$2,000 so that we bump this up to four
we add another zero that's
$40,000
$38,000 profit off of a campaign like
this and those are the types of
campaigns that we run all the time
online that's what we show our clients
how to do that's what we'll show you how
to do in my Cent growth accelerator
program and listen I'd love to have you
become a part of that I'd love to have
you work with us in my accelerator
program all right I'd love to have you
join us in there and truly see the
difference that it makes the Financial
Freedom the time Freedom being able to
dial in your messaging your marketing
they have consistency they have Clarity
to have massive impact that you can have
in your life and in your business being
able to find the right Niche be able to
figure out how do we Market be able to
figure out how do we how do we build out
some of those technical aspects in our
business me having me be able to come
alongside you and walk you through that
whole process become a part of your team
and your long-term success strategy in
your business I'd love to do that with
you I'd love to help you with that
that's what we do in my client growth
accelerator program all right and so
when you
are building a business it's your job to
put mechanisms
together to get people in the
door so let's say these 100 people
they're on your email list from there we
can have a landing page where people
sign
up off of social
media to join our email
list and we figure out okay here's how I
Market to those people on social media
and that's exactly
what you need to do this is what's
working right now this is the process
that's working right now in our business
with our clients businesses and it can
work for you as well all right so
learning the process of communicating
with people powerfully getting them to
buy into what you're offering getting
them to
truly not just say wow that's great
information but this is going to work
for me I need it I need it now and I
need to figure out how to take action
with this that's what you're looking for
Listen by the way if you'd love to jump
into my accelerator program you're
listening to this podcast right now
shoot me a DM on my Instagram you can go
find my Instagram look up Jeremiah
Kowski and tell me you want to jump in
the accelerator program all right and
I'll send you a link to be able to to go
through that process and how to do that
and be able to even give you a trial run
of it okay so if you are a coach trainer
and
Mentor keep going
don't stay stuck keep moving forward I'd
love to help you build your business and
grow it grow your life everybody and
we'll talk soon
[Music]
[Applause]